Casey Murrow Collection of Edward R. Murrow Materials MS255
Tufts Archival Research Center
Casey Murrow Collection of Edward R. Murrow Materials
1791 -- 2003
Tufts Archival Research Center
Murrow, Charles Casey
MS255
11.9 Linear Feet 7 record cartons, 1 oversize box, 2 volume boxes
The Casey Murrow Collection of Edward R. Murrow Materials contain photographs, correspondence, clippings, scrapbooks, speeches, scripts, books, and legal documents dating from 1791 to 2003. The collection documents broadcast and television journalist Edward R. Murrow's personal and professional life, as well as the lives of his wife, Janet (Brewster) Murrow, and his son, Casey Murrow.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Casey Murrow, 2018, accession number MS-2019-039, 2019, accession number MS-2019-035, and 2022, accession number MS-2023-043.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in four series: photographs and memorabilia, personal papers, professional papers, and 2022 accessions.
Series one has been arranged by format. Series two has been physically maintained in received order. Intellectually, similar materials have been grouped together, particularly where groups of photographs share a subject or location. Series three has been left in its received order, with the exception of intellectually grouping photographs of Edward R. Murrow and photographs from Murrow's time working for the U.S. Information Agency. Series four has been left in its received order.
Biographical / Historical
Edward R. Murrow (1908-1965) was a prominent CBS broadcaster during the formative years of American radio and television news programs. Stationed in London for CBS Radio from 1937 to 1946, Murrow assembled a group of erudite correspondents who came to be known as the "Murrow Boys" and included one woman, Mary Marvin Breckinridge. Murrow's and their broadcasts from London, Europe, Africa, and Asia before and during World War II set the standard for US foreign news broadcasting. They also helped shape the public's view of a war that Americans were at first reluctant to be drawn into.
Returning to the US in 1946, Murrow became one of the most renowned radio and television news broadcasters of his time. Particularly famous were his programs Hear It Now, This I Believe, Person to Person, See It Now, and Years of Crisis. Of particular note are his 1954 broadcast about Senator Joseph McCarthy's persecution of presumed Communists and his 1960 Harvest of Shame documentary depicting the plight of migrant farm workers in the US. From 1961 to January 1964 he served as the Director of the United States Information Agency (USIA). Murrow died of cancer on April 27, 1965.
Biographical / Historical
Charles Casey Murrow, known as Casey Murrow, was born on November 6, 1945 in London, England. He is the son of broadcasting journalists Edward R. Murrow and Janet Brewster Murrow.
In 1946, the Murrows left England for Massachusetts, where Casey Murrow attended Milton Academy, graduating in 1964. He received B.A. degrees in history and psychology from Yale University in 1968, and later earned an M.A. in education from Antioch College. In 1968, Murrow married Liza Ketchum, and they are the parents of two sons.
As of 2018, Murrow is Director of Synergy Learning, a nonprofit organization specializing in science and math programs for schools and teachers, and heads the Southeast Vermont Learning Collaborative, one of Vermont's six education service agencies.
Related Materials
Janet Brewster Murrow and Edward R. Murrow Family Papers, 1920-1989. Tufts University. Tufts Archival Research Center. Medford, MA.
Edward R. Murrow Papers, 1890-1992. Tufts University. Tufts Archival Research Center. Medford, MA.
Scope and Contents
The Casey Murrow Collection of Edward R. Murrow Materials contain photographs, correspondence, clippings, scrapbooks, speeches, scripts, books, and legal documents dating from 1791 to 2003. The collection documents broadcast and television journalist Edward R. Murrow's personal and professional life, as well as the lives of his wife, Janet (Brewster) Murrow, and his son, Casey Murrow.
Photographs of the Murrow family make up a significant portion of the collection, and include photos of Edward, Janet, and Casey individually and together and photographs of the extended Murrow and Brewster families. The personal papers in the collection also document the Murrow family home in Pawling, NY and of the settlement of the Murrow estate. The professional papers primarily document the work of Edward R. Murrow in London during World War II, at CBS from 1935 to 1960, and as Director of the U.S. Information Agency from 1961 to 1963. Records that date from after his death in 1965 relate to the Murrow estate, tributes and memorial events, and biographies about Murrow.
Many files in the collection include notes supplied by Casey Murrow that provide context about the subjects and individuals represented in the records, including date information.
Custodial History
Material related to the Murrow estate and biographies by Joseph E. Persico, A. M. Sperber, and Alexander Kendrick originally belonged to James M. Seward, the executor of the Murrow estate and former vice-president at CBS. This material appears to have been transferred to Janet Murrow and from her to Casey Murrow.
Other Finding Aids
Information regarding the contents of many folders was provided by Casey Murrow and remains in or attached to the relevant file. These notes include information such as the individuals and locations of photographs and the approximate or known date of photographs. This information has been incorporated into the collection description but has not been fact checked.
Family life; Media and broadcast history; Murrow, Edward R.
- Photographs and memorabilia, circa 1950 -- 1959; MS255.001; 1 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains three Murrow family photographs; a list of Person to Person participants from Variety Magazine; a drawing referencing Edward Murrow; and a promotional poster of Edward Murrow.
  Conditions Governing Access
  This series is open for research.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Gift of Casey Murrow, 2018, accession number MS-2019-039.
  - Photographs and memorabilia, circa 1950 -- 1959; MS255.001.001; 1 Linear Feet (Box 1)
    This file contains three Murrow family photographs; a list of Person to Person participants from Variety Magazine; a drawing referencing Edward Murrow; and a promotional poster of Edward Murrow.
- Personal papers, circa 1890 -- 2003; MS255.000004
  This series contains photographs, photograph albums, scrapbooks, correspondence, clippings, and legal documents. Material dates from approximately 1890 to 2003, with the bulk of the material dating from 1940 to 1965. This material documents the family lives of Edward R. Murrow, Janet (Brewster) Murrow, and Casey Murrow. Photographs of Edward, Janet, and Casey Murrow and the extended Murrow and Brewster families make up a significant portion of the series. The Murrow family is also documented through correspondence between family members; Brewster family genealogical research; records related to the Murrow family home and Glen Arden farm in Pawling, NY; and estate records, contracts, power of attorney documents, and other legal and financial records.
  Other personal items in this series include Edward R. Murrow's birth and death certificates, passport, work identification cards, high school yearbooks, and pistol permit application; Janet Murrow's address book; and World War II ration and savings books.
  Gift of Casey Murrow, 2019, accession number MS-2019-035.
  - Casey Murrow photographs, circa 1945 -- 1970; MS255.000005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 11)
    Open for research.
  - Casey Murrow photographs, circa 1945 -- 1980; MS255.000006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Casey Murrow photographs, circa 1955 -- 1965; MS255.000007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Baby Casey photo album, circa 1945 -- 1948; MS255.000008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Childhood photographs of Casey Murrow, circa 1945 -- 1959; MS255.000009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Edward R. Murrow photographs, 1930 -- 1962; MS255.000010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Edward R. Murrow photographs, circa 1940 -- 1965; MS255.000011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Edward R. Murrow in Chicago photographs, 1945 February; MS255.000012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Edward R. Murrow reading, 1947; MS255.000013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Birthday photographs, circa 1955 -- 1960; MS255.000014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Washington State College ROTC photographs, circa 1926 -- 1931; MS255.000015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Edward R. Murrow negatives, 1940 -- 1961; MS255.000016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Edward R. and Casey Murrow in Pawling photographs, circa 1956; MS255.000017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Edward R. and Casey Murrow photograph, circa 1955; MS255.000018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - ERM and Casey photos, circa 1920 -- 1983; MS255.000019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Janet Brewster Murrow photographs, 1930 -- 1999; MS255.000020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Janet Brewster Murrow formal portrait, circa 1933; MS255.000021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Janet Murrow photographs, circa 1935; MS255.000022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Janet Brewster Murrow and Ethel Lamb Murrow photographs, circa 1880 -- 1990; MS255.000023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Middletown High School debating team photographs, 1927; MS255.000024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Janet and Jane Campbell photographs, circa 1930 -- 1959; MS255.000025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Letter to Janet Murrow and photographs of Casey Murrow, 1948; MS255.000026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - International Student Service Tenth Annual Conference photograph, 1931; MS255.000027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5)
  - Edward R. and Janet Murrow early still photographs, circa 1900 -- 1945; MS255.000028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - European travel photo album, 1937; MS255.000029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Janet and Ed Murrow photo album, 1938; MS255.000030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Shopping London photographs, circa 1938 -- 1945; MS255.000031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Edward R. and Janet Murrow on board ship from NY to Southampton photographs, 1953; MS255.000032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Murrow family photographs, circa 1920 -- 1997; MS255.000033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Murrow family photographs, 1931 -- 1936; MS255.000034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Murrow family photographs, circa 1945 -- 1960; MS255.000035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Murrow family photographs, circa 1945 -- 1965; MS255.000036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Murrow family photographs, circa 1946 -- 1951; MS255.000037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Box 1)
  - Murrow family photographs, circa 1950 -- 1959; MS255.000038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Murrow family photographs, circa 1952; MS255.000039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Murrow family photo album, circa 1950 -- 1960; MS255.000040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Murrow family photographs in Chicago and New York, circa 1935 -- 1945; MS255.000041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Murrow brothers photograph, circa 1912; MS255.000042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Dewey and Donna Murrow family photographs, circa 1920 -- 1950; MS255.000043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Edward R. Murrow and brothers photographs, circa 1930 -- 1960; MS255.000044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Edward R. Murrow with father, mother, and brother Dewey photograph, circa 1942; MS255.000045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Cross U.S. trip photographs, 1956; MS255.000046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Murrow and Brewster family photographs, circa 1890 -- 1963; MS255.000047; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Murrow and Brewster family photographs, circa 1900 -- 1960; MS255.000048; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Box 2)
  - Murrow and Brewster family photographs, circa 1920 -- 1969; MS255.000049; 2 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 23-24)
  - Murrow and Brewster family photograph, circa 1920 -- 1940; MS255.000050; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Brewster family photographs, circa 1890 -- 1920; MS255.000051; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Brewster family genealogical research, 1924; MS255.000052; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Brewster family letters, circa 1910 -- 1960; MS255.000053; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Glen Arden Farm photographs, 1953 -- 1975; MS255.000054; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Pawling, first house photographs, circa 1945 -- 1955; MS255.000055; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Glen Arden Farm and Pawling, NY home records, 1948 -- 1989; MS255.000056; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Pawling clippings, newsletters, and photographs, circa 1955 -- 1985; MS255.000057; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Pawling, NY photographs, 1948 -- 1953; MS255.000058; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Edward R. Murrow birth and death certificates, 1908 -- 1965; MS255.000059; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Edward R. Murrow high school publications and diploma, 1924 -- 1926; MS255.000060; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Edward R. Murrow's first passport, 1930; MS255.000061; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Edward R. Murrow pistol permit application, 1960 -- 1962; MS255.000062; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Janet Murrow's address book, circa 1940 -- 1965; MS255.000063; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Edward R. Murrow personal correspondence, 1957; MS255.000064; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Edward R. Murrow personal correspondence, circa 1945; MS255.000065; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Edward R. Murrow and Lacey Murrow correspondence, 1940 -- 1942; MS255.000066; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Ed's mother to him letter, 1954; MS255.000067; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Ethel Lamb Murrow to Janet Murrow correspondence, 1934; MS255.000068; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Janet Murrow correspondence and cards from Churchills, circa 1956; MS255.000069; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Dr. Butler correspondence, 1941 -- 1963; MS255.000070; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Lewis Power letter to Janet Murrow, 1989; MS255.000071; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Letter from Agnes Conwell to Janet Murrow, 1922; MS255.000072; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Letter from Edward R. to Janet Murrow, circa 1945; MS255.000073; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Janet Murrow correspondence, 1965; MS255.000074; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Casey Murrow financial documents, 1964 -- 1965; MS255.000075; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 20)
    75 years from date of creation.
  - Edward R. Murrow power of attorney documents, 1942 -- 1953; MS255.000076; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Janet Murrow power of attorney documents, 1966; MS255.000077; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Murrow trust agreements, 1956 -- 1966; MS255.000078; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Murrow estate records, 1979 -- 1980; MS255.000079; 5 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 30-34)
  - Murrow, E.R. - Personal Contracts J.M.S. (James M. Seward), circa 1950 -- 1959; MS255.000080; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Murrow estate - CBS contracts, 1966 -- 1978; MS255.000081; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Murrow estate executed contracts, 1968 -- 1969; MS255.000082; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - World War II ration and savings books, circa 1940 -- 1945; MS255.000083; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Pam Am tickets, 1942 -- 1943; MS255.000084; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Major C. B. Ormerod signed portrait, 1957 December; MS255.000085; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Larry LeSuer obituary and memorial service program, 2003; MS255.000086; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Professional papers, 1920 -- 2002; MS255.000087
  This series contains photographs, clippings, correspondence, contracts and other legal documents, speeches, scripts, and proposals for biographical works on Edward R. Murrow. The material dates from 1920 to 2002, with the bulk dating from the 1930s to 1970s, several years after Edward R. Murrow's death. This series primarily documents the professional work of Edward R. Murrow in London during World War II, at CBS from 1935 to 1960, and as Director of the U.S. Information Agency from 1961 to 1963. Photographs and correspondence document his work as a broadcast and television journalist, including his highly publicized conflict with Senator Joseph McCarthy in 1954.
  Janet Murrow's professional life is represented in this series through photographs and other records of her reporting work in London during World War II. Legal documents and correspondence reflect Janet Murrow's role in managing the Murrow estate after Edward R. Murrow's death in 1965. There are proposals for biographical works about Edward R. Murrow, including books, television shows, film, and plays, photographs and ephemera from events to honor Murrow, and litigation related to the use of the Murrow family name. Photographs and correspondence document Casey Murrow's presence at events in honor of Edward R. Murrow and invitations to speak about his father. Material relating to the Murrow estate and biographies on Edward R. Murrow appears to have been transferred from CBS to Janet Murrow and later to Casey Murrow.
  Significant figures who are featured in the photographs in this series include U.S. Presidents Harry Truman, Dwight D. Eisenhower, John F. Kennedy, and Lyndon B. Johnson; Israeli Prime Minister David Ben-Gurion; Senator Joseph McCarthy; CBS newsmen Fred Friendly and William Paley; and other politicians and television personalities.
  - Edward R. Murrow photographs, 1930 -- 1962; MS255.000088; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Edward R. Murrow photographs, circa 1930 -- 1965; MS255.000089; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Edward R. Murrow photographs, circa 1940 -- 1960; MS255.000090; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Edward R. Murrow photographs, circa 1940 -- 1965; MS255.000091; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Edward R. Murrow negatives, 1940 -- 1961; MS255.000092; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Edward R. Murrow photographs, 1947; MS255.000093; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Edward R. Murrow photographs, 1949; MS255.000094; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Edward R. Murrow photographs, circa 1950 -- 1974; MS255.000095; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Edward R. Murrow photographs and clippings, circa 1962 -- 1984; MS255.000096; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - U.S. Information Agency photographs of Edward R. Murrow and Tom Sorenson, 1960 -- 1963; MS255.000097; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Information Agency photographs of Edward R. Murrow, 1960 -- 1963; MS255.000098; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Information Agency photographs of Edward R. Murrow, 1960 -- 1963; MS255.000099; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - U.S. Information Agency era pictures, circa 1960 -- 1963; MS255.000100; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Kennedy-era - D.C. photographs of Murrows, circa 1961 -- 1963; MS255.000101; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - John F. Kennedy and Edward R. Murrow photograph, circa 1961 -- 1963; MS255.000102; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Director, US Information Agency photographs, circa 1960 -- 1963; MS255.000103; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - 20th Anniversary - American Library London photographs, 1963 May; MS255.000104; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Ditchley Conference, 1963 May; MS255.000105; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - U.S. Information Agency South American and Caribbean trip photographs, circa 1963; MS255.000106; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - U.S. Information Agency photographs, circa 1960 -- 1963; MS255.000107; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - US Information Agency publications, circa 1960 -- 1963; MS255.000108; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - U.S. Information Agency trip to Haiti - Ed to Casey correspondence, circa 1960 -- 1963; MS255.000109; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Edward R. Murrow postage stamp clippings and correspondence, 1994; MS255.000110; 2 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 4-5)
  - Murrow: A Treatment script by Ernest Kinoy, circa 1980; MS255.000111; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Skagit County Historical Museum event invitation, 2002; MS255.000112; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Edward R. Murrow clippings scrapbook, 1941 -- 1945; MS255.000113; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Landsburg TV Film, Good Night and Good Luck script, 1975 -- 1976; MS255.000114; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - "Ike Backs Murrow" photocopy of news headline, 1954; MS255.000115; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Overseas Press Club presenting idea of Murrow memorial, 1968; MS255.000116; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Edward R. Murrow photographs, clippings, and Freedom Award acceptance speech, 1954 -- 1994; MS255.000117; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Edward R. Murrow news and photographs, 1941 -- 1962; MS255.000118; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Jefferson/Columbia Records Inc. - I Can Hear It Now Royalty (The Cold War and The Atomic Age) records, 1956 -- 1957; MS255.000119; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Brown - John Sharnick correspondence, 1981 -- 1983; MS255.000120; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Clippings scrapbook, 1956-1958; MS255.000121; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Berlin trip correspondence and script, 1948; MS255.000122; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - CBS memo from Edward R. Murrow to Seward, 1949 December; MS255.000123; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Israel reporting, 1956; MS255.000124; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Telegrams sent to Edward R. Murrow after McCarthy broadcast, 1953 March; MS255.000125; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Edward R. Murrow biography proposals, 1965 -- 1967; MS255.000126; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Ed - 2 speeches before leaving CBS, 1961 January; MS255.000127; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Greensboro, North Carolina historic marker and avenue, 1990; MS255.000128; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Ed at Washington State, circa 1950 -- 1959; MS255.000129; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Travels for Institute for International Education, 1932 -- 1935; MS255.000130; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Winston Burdett, Edward R. Murrow, and Bill Sherer photograph, circa 1939; MS255.000131; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Edward R. Murrow in London during WWII photographs, circa 1938 -- 1945; MS255.000132; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Edward R. Murrow in London photograph, 1938 May; MS255.000133; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - World War II photographs, circa 1938 -- 1945; MS255.000134; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Janet Murrow WWII reporting and photographs, circa 1938 -- 1945; MS255.000135; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Ed and Bill Shirer, 1946; MS255.000136; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Ed at West Point photographs, circa 1946; MS255.000137; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Interview with Field Marshall Montgomery photographs, circa 1950 -- 1959; MS255.000138; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Korea trip photographs, 1950 -- 1952; MS255.000139; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Pictures - Israel, circa 1952; MS255.000140; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Edward R. Murrow CBS photographs, circa 1940 -- 1955; MS255.000141; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - "A Report on Senator Joseph R. McCarthy" printed script and photograph of Edward R. Murrow, circa 1954; MS255.000142; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Berlin trip photographs, 1953 September; MS255.000143; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Ed Murrow Korea photographs, 1953; MS255.000144; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 44)